const questions = [{
    question: 'What decade is "Stranger Things" set in?',
    option1: '1950s',
    option2: '1960s',
    option3: '1970s',
    option4: '1980s',
    option5: '1990s',
    answer: 4
},

{ 
    question: 'What is the order of the words Terry keeps repeating when Eleven visits her?',
    option1: 'Breathe. Sunflower. Three to the right, four to the left. Rainbow. 450.', 
    option2: 'Sunflower. Rainbow. Breathe. 450. Three to the right, four to the left.',
    option3: 'Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow. Three to the right, four to the left. 450.',
    option4: 'Rainbow. Breathe. 450. Sunflower. Three to the right, four to the left.',
    option5: 'Three to the right, four to the left. 450. Rainbow. Breathe. Sunflower.',
    answer: 1
},

{
    question: 'What do the kids name the creature Dustin finds in his garbage?',
    option1: 'The Shadow Monster',
    option2: 'Thessalhydra',
    option3: 'Demogorgon',
    option4: 'Mind Flayer',
    option5: 'Pollywog',
    answer: 5
},      

{
    question: 'Who did Barb’s parents hire to find their “missing” daughter?',
    option1: 'Jim Hopper',
    option2: 'Calvin Powell',
    option3: 'Phil Callahan',
    option4: 'Bob Newby',
    option5: 'Murray Bauman',
    answer: 5
},

{
    question: 'What is the name of the road where Will disappears?',
    option1: 'Mirkwood',
    option2: 'Cornwallis',
    option3: 'Kerley',
    option4: 'Forest',
    option5: 'Maple',
    answer: 1
},

{
    question: 'In what video game does Maxine beat Dustin’s high score?',
    option1: 'Pac-man',
    option2: 'Tetris',
    option3: 'Space invaders',
    option4: 'Dig dug',
    option5: 'Galaga',
    answer: 4
},

{
    question: 'What is the name of the project Eleven was a part of?',
    option1: 'Project MKUltra',
    option2: 'Stargate Project',
    option3: 'Operation Momentum',
    option4: 'Project Azorian',
    option5: 'Project FUBELT',
    answer: 1
},

{
    question: 'What is the name of the town “Stranger Things” is set in?',
    option1: 'Hopkins',
    option2: 'Hawkins',
    option3: 'Hartford',
    option4: 'Hamilton',
    option5: 'Hamburg',
    answer: 2
},

{
    question: 'What is the name of Dustin’s cat?',
    option1: 'Fluffy',
    option2: 'Luna',
    option3: 'Mews',
    option4: 'Dart',
    option5: 'Kitty',
    answer: 3
},

{
    question: 'What is Jonathan and Will’s favorite song?',
    option1: '“How Soon Is Now” by The Smiths',
    option2: '“Atmosphere” by Joy Division',
    option3: '“See No Evil” by Television',
    option4: '“Let’s Dance” by David Bowie',
    option5: '“Should I Stay or Should I Go” by The Clash',
    answer: 5
}]